worldewallet.com 2015-03-15

# World eWallet - Privacy - Global eWallet Solution

The World eWallet Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes how World eWallet manages a World eWallet User's personal information. By visiting or using the World eWallet Service website, www.worldewallet.com or other World eWallet website (each and all, the “Site”) and use of any of the associated tools or applications, you, as a User, are expressly agreeing to, and signify consent and acceptance of the Policy. World eWallet is committed to respecting and preserving your privacy at all times and the Policy will inform you of how information is collected, stored, used, and protected as well as the limited circumstances under which a World eWallet User's information may be shared with others. The Policy will also instruct on how you can contact World eWallet regarding questions or concerns relating to the Policy.

The Policy describes the ways World eWallet collects, stores, uses and protects a World eWallet User's personal information. As a User of the World eWallet Service, you accept the Policy and consent to such collection, storage and use when you sign up for and the use of the World eWallet Service, products, or any other feature, technologies or functionalities offered by the Site or through any other means (collectively “World eWallet Services”). 

World eWallet may amend the Policy at any time by posting a revised version on the World eWallet Site. The revised version will be effective at the time it is posted and will supersede any previous versions of the Policy. In addition, if the revised version includes a substantial change, World eWallet will provide you with 30 days' prior notice by posting notice on our Site. After this 30 days' notice, you, the User, will be considered as having expressly consented to all amendments to the Policy.

1.

Collection. When you, the World eWallet User, use the World eWallet Site or message a member of World eWallet, the personal information collected that you provide may include:

  * your name, email address, address, contact phone number(s);
  * IP address and standard web log-in information; and
  * Any other information you provide when using the Site.

Our servers are located in various places, including the “cloud”. If you choose to provide personal information, then you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on World eWallet servers.

2.

Use. A User's personal information is used to:

  * provide the World eWallet Service;
  * resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our policies;
  * customize a User's experience, inform Users about services and updates, and measure interest in the World eWallet Services;
  * communicate with World eWallet Users about Site updates and information; and/or
  * send World eWallet Service and Site related information.

3.

Disclosure. World eWallet does not sell or rent a User's personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without a User's explicit consent. World eWallet may combine a User's information with information collected from other companies and use it to improve and personalize the World eWallet Services, content and advertising. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from World eWallet or participate, then indicate your preference by following the unsubscribe/opt out directions provided with the communication. World eWallet may disclose a User's personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce World eWallet policies, respond to claims that a User's activity may violate another Users’ rights, or protect all User's rights, property, or safety. World eWallet may also share a User's personal information with service providers who help with our business operations and with members of our corporate family who may provide joint content and services and help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts.

4.

Access, Modification, and Deletion. Except as required by applicable laws, World eWallet will delete a User's personal information when it no longer is needed for the purposes described above or for any other purposes the User may authorize. We retain a User's personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes and enforce our policies. To access or correct your personal information, please contact World eWallet at info@worldewallet.com.

5.

Security. World eWallet uses the industry standard protection tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect a User's personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but World eWallet does not guarantee, and you, as a User, should not expect that your personal information will remain private. World eWallet is not responsible for any privacy policies or data practices of any third party websites, including without limitation any social networking website or service

## How a User’s information is collected 

When a World eWallet User visits and logs in or accesses the World eWallet Site or uses the World eWallet Services, World eWallet collects that User’s IP address and standard web login information, such as the web browser type and the pages a User has accessed on the World eWallet Site.

If you open an account and use the World eWallet Services, the following types of information, but not limited to this list, is collected: 

  * Contact information – full name, address, phone, email and other similar information.
  * Valid government issued photo identification
  * Proof of Address
  * Financial information - the full bank account numbers that is linked to your World eWallet account or provide to World eWallet when you use the World eWallet Services
  * “Know Your Client” information for AML and similar regulatory compliance purposes

Before you can access and use the World eWallet Services, you must provide additional information that we can use to verify your identity or address or manage risk, such as your date of birth, valid government issued photo identification and proof of address. World eWallet may also obtain information pertaining to you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification services.

When a World eWallet User is using the World eWallet Services, World eWallet collects information about a User’s account electronic transactions and may also collect information about a User’s computer or other access devices used to access the World eWallet Services for fraud prevention purposes.

World eWallet may also collect additional information from a User in other ways, such as through contacts with the World eWallet Customer Support Team, results of surveys and interactions with any member of the World eWallet corporate family or other companies.

## How are cookies used

When a World eWallet User accesses the World eWallet Site, World eWallet, or companies that are hired to track how the World eWallet Services are used, may place small data files called “cookies” on your computer.

A “cookie” is sent to your computer when you log in to the Site and access your account, or otherwise use the World eWallet Services. This type of cookie helps World eWallet to recognize you, as a valid User, and when multiple web pages are visited on the World eWallet Site during the same session, so that you are not asked for your personal password on each page. Once you log out or close the web browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect.

World eWallet may also use longer-lasting cookies for other purposes such as to display your e-mail address on the sign-in form, so that you don’t need to retype the e-mail address each time you log in to your account.

World eWallet encodes the cookies so that only World eWallet can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline the World eWallet cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with the use of the World eWallet Site and Services or products offered by World eWallet.

World eWallet and our service-providers also use cookies to customize the World eWallet Services, content and advertising, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety.

You may also encounter cookies from third parties when using the World eWallet Services on websites that we do not control (for example, if you view a webpage created by a third party or use an application developed by a third party, there may be a cookie placed by that web page or application). 

## How we protect and store personal information

Throughout this policy, the term “personal information” is used to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and is used to identify that person. World eWallet does not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific individual. 

World eWallet will store and process a User’s personal information on computers and elsewhere in the world where World eWallet has facilities. World eWallet protects that personal information by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable law. World eWallet uses computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, restricts physical access to our buildings and files, and restricts access to personal information so that only those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities have such access. 

## How a User’s personal information that is collected is then used

The primary purpose for collecting a User’s personal information is to provide a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience using the World eWallet Services and the Site. 

To that end, a User’s personal information is used to:

  * provide the Services and customer support that is requested;
  * process transactions and send notices about electronic transactions;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce the Agreement;
  * customize, measure, and improve the World eWallet Services and the content and layout of the Site;
  * deliver targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on a World eWallet User’s communication preferences; and
  * compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.

## How a User’s personal information is shared with other World eWallet Users

To process requested electronic transfer requests, World eWallet must share some of a User’s personal information with the person or beneficiary that the User is sending funds to or receiving funds from. Information shared includes a User’s contact information, the transaction date, the amount of the transaction, and whether the User has verified control of an external personal bank account that has been provided to World eWallet when an account is opened with World eWallet to transact through the World eWallet Services. 

World eWallet works with third parties to enable them to accept or facilitate payments from or to a World eWallet User using the World eWallet Service. In doing so, a third party may share information about a World eWallet User with us, such as an email address or phone number to inform or confirm that an electronic transaction that you had requested is processed through that third party service. World eWallet uses your personal information to confirm that you are a valid World eWallet User. World eWallet will send a notification message to you that the electronic transaction you requested is made and processed. 

## How personal information is shared with others

World eWallet may share a User’s personal information with:

  * Members of the World eWallet Inc. corporate family – like World eWallet.com – to provide joint content, products and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about products, services and communications. Members of the World eWallet corporate family will use this information to send marketing communications.

  * Service providers under contract who help with parts of World eWallet business operations; (fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, technology services). The contracts dictate that these service providers only use a User’s information in connection with the services they perform for World eWallet and not for their own benefit.

  * Companies that World eWallet plans to merge with or be acquired by (should such a combination occur) World eWallet will require that the new combined entity follow the Policy with respect to protecting a World eWallet User’s personal information. If a User’s personal information could be used contrary to the Policy, you, the User, will receive prior notice and an opportunity to withdraw consent.

  * Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when:
    1. World eWallet is compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure;
    2. World eWallet needs to do so to comply with applicable law;
    3. World eWallet believes in good faith that the disclosure of a User’s personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of the Agreement.

  * Other third parties with a User’s consent or direction to do so.

NOTE: IF YOU OPEN A WORLD EWALLET ACCOUNT DIRECTLY ON A THIRD PARTY WEBSITE OR VIA A THIRD PARTY APPLICATION, ANY INFORMATION THAT YOU ENTER ON THAT WEBSITE OR APPLICATION (AND NOT DIRECTLY ON THE WORLD EWALLET SITE) WILL BE SHARED WITH THE OWNER OF THE THIRD PARTY WEBSITE OR APPLICATION AND YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE SUBJECT TO THE THIRD PARTY’S PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY SOCIAL NETWORKING WEBSITE OR SERVICE. WE RECOMMEND THAT YOU ALWAYS DEAL DIRECTLY WITH THE WORLD EWALLET SITE. 

There may be links to other websites on the World eWallet Site which may or may not have a privacy policy. World eWallet is not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through third party websites or application and expressly disclaim any responsibility or liability related to such collection, use or disclosure. Please note that these third parties may be in other countries where the laws on processing personal information may be less stringent than in your country. 

## How a User can contact World eWallet about Privacy Policy related questions

If you have questions or concerns regarding the Policy, you can contact World eWallet at info@worldewallet.com.
